Who the hell are you?
（里見(さとみ)蓮太郎(れんたろう)）てめえは 誰だ
The one who got in my way...
Just who are you?
（ティナ）
私を邪魔した あなたは…
誰？
♪～
～♪
#06 Tragic Irony
（あくび）
（足音）
Here, I bought this for you.
（蓮太郎）ほらよ
買ってきてやったぞ
Thank you very much.
ありがとうございます
（蓮太郎）フゥ…
I don't mind that you called and asked
me to show you around this area,
この辺 案内してほしいって
連絡してくるのはいいけど
but could you not ask to go
the same day you call me?
当日の朝はやめとけよ
It's way too sudde—
いくらなんでも 急すぎ…
ん？ おい 何やって…
Hey, what are you—
I don't handle waking up early too well.
（ティナ）早起きは苦手で…
Should I not have?
ダメでしたか？
It's fine.
いいよ
The sniper last night...
昨日の狙撃…
Traitor
I'll kill you
I did some research on people likely
to try to assassinate Seitenshi, but...
聖天子(せいてんし)暗殺を
もくろむようなヤツらを―
Death to the one
trying to give rights
to the Gastrea
調べてみたが…
ハァ…
They're not it... That enemy is...
違う あいつは…
a much more dangerous one.
もっと 危険な敵だ
Give me a hint...
なんとか 手がかりくらいは…
（ティナ）ああっ
（たこ焼きが落ちる音）
あ…
（ティナ）あう…
（蓮太郎）あっ
あ…
あ… ちょっと貸せ
Let me see it.
あう…
ハァ…
Rentaro-san, more, please.
蓮太郎さん もっと下さい
ハァ…
フッ… フフッ…
There, all clean.
（蓮太郎）よし キレイになった
Thank you very much.
Today was a lot of fun.
（ティナ）ありがとうございます
今日は楽しかったです
It's fine.
（蓮太郎）いいよ
I had a lot happen yesterday, myself,
俺も 昨日は
なんか いろいろあったし
so this was a nice change of pace.
いい気分転換になった
I like you, Rentaro-san.
私 蓮太郎さんのこと好きです
H-Huh?
は… はあ？
This is the first time anyone's
been so nice to me... I think.
私 こんなに優しくされたの
生まれて初めて… かなと
It hasn't been very fun
since my parents died.
私は 両親が死んでから―
あまり楽しくない気分です
My life is nothing but pain...
私の人生は 痛いだけです
So, right now,
だから 今
久しぶりに楽しい気分です
this feels like the most fun
I've had in a long time.
Say, Tina...
なあ ティナ…
（携帯電話の着信音）
あっ
I have to go.
私 もう行かなきゃ
Can we meet again?
また 会えますか？
Yeah... Give me a call again sometime.
ああ また電話してこいよ
フフッ…
You're late.
（マスター）遅いぞ
I've obtained the plans for the next meeting.
次回の会談の計画書が流れてきた
Those civil officers...
あの民警は？
I've found out who they are.
（マスター）
ヤツらの正体も分かった
Tina Sprout, you have a new mission.
ティナ･スプラウト
新たな任務だ
Kill the president of the
Tendo Civil Security Agency,
直ちに
天童(てんどう)民間警備会社の社長―
Tendo Kisara, immediately.
天童木更(きさら)を殺害せよ
Yes, Master.
はい マスター
（チャイム）
Student Council Office
That cake the other day...
（女子生徒たちの話し声）
Yeah, it was great!
（女子生徒たち）あっ
（蓮太郎）ん？
Listen carefully, Satomi-kun.
（天童木更）いい？ 里見くん
After we toss in the tear-gas canister,
催涙弾を転がしたあと
we're going to shoot Miori
when she comes strolling out.
ノコノコ出てきた未織(みおり)を
２人して射殺するわよ
Two in the chest, and one to the head.
胸に２発 頭に１発 撃ち込んで
We're going to make that woman history.
あの女を この世から
おさらばさせるの
Sorry, but could you wait outside?
悪いんだけど 外で待ってろよ
N-No! I can't leave you alone with Miori!
（木更）ダ… ダメ！
未織と里見くんを
２人きりにはできないわ
Hey, Satomi-kun!
あっ ちょっと 里見くん！
う… うわっ！
（木更）ああっ くっ…
Welcome, Satomi-chan.
（司馬(しば)未織）
いらっしゃい 里見ちゃん
Miori! Open this door at once!
（木更）未織 今すぐ開けなさい！
Otherwise, I'm breaking it down!
じゃないと 扉 破るわよ！
I'll be sure to bill your office for the damages.
請求書は そっちに
きっちり送らせてもらうで
うっ… うう～
Well, then... Let's go next door.
（未織）ほな 隣に行こか
The bullet the sniper used was
（未織）
狙撃に使われていたのは―
from a .50 caliber Browning
heavy machine gun.
50口径のブローニング
重機関銃用の弾やった
The rifling was clean.
ライフリングはクリーン
No record of it being used in previous crimes.
犯罪使用歴はない
Considering the angle,
このビルから撃ったのは
ほぼ間違いないんやけど…
I'm almost certain it was
fired from this building, but...
To be honest,
ハッキリ言って
it's pretty much impossible
to hit something with two
この距離から ２発の徹甲弾を
当てるなんて芸当は 不可能や
sniper bullets from this distance.
Who are they?
何者なんだ 一体
Satomi-chan, you should be careful!
里見ちゃん
気ぃつけたほうがええ！
It's clear the enemy is an
impossibly skilled sniper.
敵は 間違いなく
超ド級のスナイパーや
In comparison, Seitenshi's bodyguards
are from an infant organization
それに比べ 聖天子付護衛官は
発足して 僅か10年弱しか
稼働していない
that was only founded in the last ten years.
ひよっこ組織
With things as they are,
こんな状態じゃ―
it wouldn't be surprising if Seitenshi-sama
were to die any day now.
いつ聖天子様が お命落としても
おかしくないで
Miori, would you do some
research on Saitake Sogen?
未織
斉武宗玄(さいたけそうげん)について
調べてくれないか
He's the one who hired the assassin.
あいつが 今回の暗殺の依頼人だ
Satomi-chan, you're such a kidder...
里見ちゃんも言うわ～
Can't I ask you to have my back?
お前のほうで
裏を固められないか！
（未織）ん～
But we're talking about the head
of state of the Osaka Area here...
仮にも 大阪エリアの
国家元首が相手やしなあ
All right.
分かった
But in return...
その代わり…
I want you to show me your true power.
里見ちゃんの本当の力
うちにも見せてほしいな
That has nothing to do with you.
お前には関係ねえだろ！
Besides, that's not something I show just anyone.
だいたい あれは
他人に見せるようなものじゃねえ
Do you prefer Kisara that much?
そんなに 木更がええの？
If you were able to forget about Kisara,
木更のこと忘れられるなら
you can do whatever you want
to my body, Satomi-chan...
うちの体 里見ちゃんの
思うようにしても ええんやで
うっ…
（２人）うわっ
What are you two doing?!
何やってんのよ あんたたち！
（蓮太郎）あ？
（未織）フゥ…
It's not... Th-This isn't anything!
違っ！ こ…
これは なんでもない！
Don't get the wrong idea, Kisara.
誤解せんでな 木更
All right, Satomi-chan,
じゃ 里見ちゃん
I'll be going ahead with
what we talked about earlier.
あの話 このまま
進めさせてもらうで
What did we talk about earlier?!
（蓮太郎）
な… なんだよ あの話って！
Why, of course...
何って…
うちが体 差し出したら―
That you'd transfer to my company
if I offered myself up for you.
里見ちゃんが
うちの会社に移籍するって
えっ？ ウソ…
You're kidding...
Oh, Kisara. It's really nothing.
あっ 木更
ほんまに なんでもないんよ
Well, I'll be leaving now.
じゃあ うちは これで
Hey!
おいっ！
（未織）フフッ
Kisara-san, that really wasn't
what it sounded like...
木更さん
今のは ホントに違うんだ！
You idiot!
おバカー！
（室戸(むろと) 菫(すみれ)）フッハハハハ…
You seem happy, Sensei.
うれしそうだな 先生
Of course.
（菫）当然だ
A bug fanatic with a pity-me face
like yours is unworthy of
木更は 君みたいな
不幸面の虫マニアには
prime real estate like Kisara-kun.
もったいない物件だ
It's hard to believe she
doesn't have a boyfriend yet.
まだ 彼氏がいないのが
不思議なくらいだよ
You should be trying a bit harder.
もっと 焦ったらどうだ？
Though you're rude,
you are quite the gentleman...
君は ぞんざいなわりに
フェミニストだが
But you lack the nerve to
push through a woman's hesitation
女性のためらいを
あえて押し切って獲得するだけの
and make her yours.
征服欲というものが欠けている
That's your downfall, Rentaro-kun.
それは 君の欠点だよ
蓮太郎くん
Shut up.
（藍原延珠(あいはらえんじゅ)）イッシシ～
（蓮太郎）うっせえ
What did you want to talk about
だいたい 延珠まで呼んで
一体 なんの話だよ！
that you had to call Enju here for?
This is late, but congratulations.
（菫）遅れたけど おめでとう
I hear you've defeated Hiruko Kagetane,
君は 蛭子(ひるこ)影胤(かげたね)を倒し
序列1000番という
and reached the rank of
1,000, making you one of
高位序列者に
加わったそうじゃないか
the higher ranking individuals.
And so... I thought I'd talk to you about
そこでだ
君に 私以外の３人の天才について
話しておこうと思ってね
the three prodigies other than me.
The other three prodigies?
３人の天才？
Rentaro-kun, who do you recognize me as?
（菫）蓮太郎くん
君は 私をどういう人物だと
認識している？
The person who is the
former chief executive of
（蓮太郎）新人類創造計画の
元最高責任者
the New Humanity Creation Plan.
I can only give you partial
credit for that answer.
（菫）その回答では
部分点しかあげられんな
The New Humanity Creation Plan is the name
新人類創造計画とは
of a mechanized soldier
project plan that was
日本を含む
４か国共同で行われた
a joint effort between four
countries, including Japan.
機械化兵士計画のプロジェクト名だ
From the Australian division, Arthur Zanuck.
オーストラリア支部の
アーサー･ザナック
From the American division, "Next," Ayn Rand.
アメリカ支部“NEXT”の
エイン･ランド
From the Japanese division,
Muroto Sumire. That'd be me.
日本支部の 室戸 菫
つまり 私だな
And the one who brought us all together,
そして それらを統括する―
Albrecht Grünewald from Germany.
ドイツの
アルブレヒト･グリューネワルト
These four were gathered to protect
the world from the Gastrea invasion.
この４人が
ガストレアの侵略から―
世界を守るために集められた
However, the project quickly dissolved.
しかし プロジェクトは
程なく解散した
Because we realized how high the
fighting ability of the Cursed Children was.
呪われた子供たちの
戦闘力の高さに気づいたからだ
It hasn't been addressed publicly,
公になっていないが―
but many of the mechanized
soldiers that were relieved
任を解かれた機械化兵士の多くは
プロモーターとなった
from duty became Promoters.
They make up most of the
higher ranking individuals.
超高位序列者のほとんどは
そういう連中だ
If you've decided to pursue your origins,
君が自分の出自を追うと
決めたならば
you're going to run into them.
遠からず 連中とも
ぶつかることになる
You should be prepared.
覚悟をしておいたほうがいい
Rentaro...
蓮太郎…
However, it's nothing to
be pessimistic about.
（菫）だが
そう悲観するものでもない
You've already defeated a mechanized soldier
君は すでに４人の１人
that was created by Grünewald,
one of the four prodigies.
天才グリューネワルト翁の
機械化兵士を倒している
（蓮太郎）はっ
Hiruko Kagetane!
蛭子影胤！
Then that means Rentaro's a
super prodigy himself, right?
じゃあ 蓮太郎は
大天才ってことなのだな！
No, that was more a miracle than anything.
いや あれは ほとんど
奇跡みたいなもんだったし
I bet.
（菫）だろうな
（延珠）あ…
You really are a jerk, Sensei.
（蓮太郎）先生って
ホントにイヤなヤツだよな
Of course. You just realized that?
当たり前だ
いまさら気づいたのか
ハァ…
We're going home, Enju.
帰るぞ 延珠
What? I came all this way and
we're already going home?
えー？ せっかく 妾(わらわ)も来たのに
もう おしまいか？
No, I'd like you to stay, Enju-chan.
（菫）いや
延珠ちゃんは残ってくれ
I want to ask you some questions.
ちょっと聞きたいことがある
I'm done with you, though, Rentaro-kun.
蓮太郎くん
君は もういいよ
You should hurry back and get
Kisara in a good mood again.
早く帰って
木更のご機嫌でも取るんだな
Tendo Kisara is the granddaughter
of Tendo Kikunojo.
（マスター）天童木更は
あの 天童菊之丞(きくのじょう)の孫娘だ
She is a master of the Tendo Martial
Arts and an expert in iaido.
天童流の免許皆伝で 居合の達人
But she is no match for you.
だが お前の敵ではない
Who was it that got in my way back there?
あのとき 私の邪魔をしたのは？
A pair from the Tendo Civil Security Agency.
（マスター）天童民間警備会社に
籍を置くペアだ
The Initiator's name is Aihara Enju.
イニシエーターの名前は 藍原延珠
The Promoter's name is—
プロモーターのほうは…
（背中が押される音）
I'm sorry, Master. What did you just say?
（ティナ）あ…
すみません マスター
今 なんと…
（不通音）
What the heck?
（木更）何よ！
I'll fire Satomi-kun myself!
里見くんなんか
こっちから解雇よ 解雇！
Even if he comes back,
I'm never going to forgive him!
戻ってきたって
絶対 許してなんかやらないから！
Damn it...
ったく！
ん？
You are Tendo Kisara, correct?
あなたが天童木更ですね？
Y-Yes... Who are you?
えっ？ ええ あなたは？
Prepare yourself.
お覚悟を
（木更）あっ
とーっ！
あ…
（木更）ん…
Too slow.
（ティナ）遅い
うっ…
うう…
Just who are you?
あなたは… 誰？
That does not matter to you,
since you're about to die.
これから死ぬ あなたには
関係ありません
あ…
You're... scared to kill someone, aren't you?
あなた 人を殺すのが
怖いんでしょ？
あっ…
あっ… ああっ
Help... me...
助けて…
Help me... Satomi-kun...
助けて 里見くん…
はっ… 里見？
"Satomi"...
Help me, Satomi-kun!
助けて 里見くん！
Inzen: Kokutenfu!
隠禅(いんぜん)･黒天風(こくてんふう)
ハァ ハァ ハァ…
It can't be...
ウソ…
あ… ティナ？
Tina...
Why?
どうして…
Why, Rentaro-san?
どうしてなんですか
蓮太郎さん
I see... so you're...
そうか お前が…
うっ…
くっ…
Rentaro-san, I...
蓮太郎さん 私は…
Rentaro-san...
蓮太郎さん…
Listen to me!
話を聞いて！
ううっ…
Kisara-san, cut the floor!
木更さん 床を斬れー！
あっ
Unebiko Yusei:
雲嶺毘却雄星(うねびこゆうせい)
Yukikage!
雪影(ゆきかげ)！
Rentaro-san...
蓮太郎さん…
Did we win?
勝ったの？
We didn't win. She ran away.
勝ったんじゃない
逃げてくれたんだ
You know her?
知り合いだったの？
Yeah...
（蓮太郎）ああ
Satomi-kun...
里見くん？
うっ…
Kisara-san?
木更さん？
Kisara-san?! Kisara-san!
木更さん… 木更さん！
（木更）うっ…
（透析装置の作動音）
I didn't want you to see
me like this, Rentaro-kun..
こういうところ
里見くんには
見せたくなかったんだけど
Like that matters right now.
いまさらだろ？
You won't consider getting a kidney operation?
腎臓の手術 受ける気はないのか？
It's not that easy to find a donor.
ドナーなんて
簡単に見つからないわよ
Not to mention...
それに…
When my body ended up this way,
この体になったとき
I decided I'd spend
私の命は全て
my life trying to rid the world
of the Tendo name.
天童を この世から葬るためだけに
使うって決めたの
If I were to forget this pain, I would
probably forget to exact revenge.
この痛みを忘却してしまったら
私 きっと 復讐(ふくしゅう)を忘れてしまうわ
（透析装置の電子音）
More importantly,
（木更）そんなことより―
I've learned something from watching Miori.
未織の行動を見ていて
私も １つだけ学んだの
S-So, Satomi-kun, you can...
だ… だから 里見くん 手を…
You can hold my hand.
手を握っていいわよ
Huh?
は？
What? That's not enough for you?
何よ 気に入らないの？
Holding hands is pretty hard to do!
手を握るって
結構 大変なことなのよ！
How?
どこが？
Because... I-It's like we're a couple...
だって…
こ… 恋人みたいじゃない
（蓮太郎）うっ…
Hurry... I'm so embarrassed, I could die.
早くして！
恥ずかしくて死んじゃいそう
But you lack the nerve to
push through a woman's hesitation
君は 女性のためらいを
あえて押し切って
相手を獲得するだけの
征服欲というものが欠けている
and make her yours.
K-Kisara-san.
き… 木更さん
ん…
ああっ
H-Hey, Satomi-kun...
ちょ… ちょっと 里見くん！
Where are you touching?
どこ触ってるの？
I didn't intend to let you go that far...
私 そこまで許すつもりじゃ…
The size, shape, elasticity...
ぬぅ… この大きさ 形 弾力
I hate to admit it, but I'd
have to give them a triple A+.
悔しいが トリプルＡ＋を
付けねばなるまい
Huh?
ええっ!?
E-Enju-chan, what are you doing?!
え… 延珠ちゃん 何してるの!?
That's what I'd like to ask you!
聞きたいのは 妾のほうだ！
When I went to the office,
it was full of holes,
事務所に帰ったら
穴だらけになってるし
and when I got here,
you had your boobs out,
ここへ来たら
木更がおっぱい放り出して―
trying to seduce Rentaro...
蓮太郎を誘惑しているし！
I do not have them out,
nor am I trying to seduce anyone!
（木更）放り出しても
誘惑もしていないわよ！
There's no doubt that the attack
（木更）今日の事務所襲撃と―
on the office today and the assassination
attempt on Seitenshi-sama are linked.
聖天子様 暗殺未遂が
リンクしているのは―
間違いない
We'll have to take responsibility
since we let the suspect get away.
犯人を取り逃がしたけじめは―
きっちりつけなきゃ
If I had been there, I'd have gone
after them and apprehended them.
（延珠）妾がいたら
追っかけて捕まえたのに
By the way, what did Sensei have to say?
そういや 先生の話って
なんだったんだ？
I'm not quite sure.
よく分からん
Something about my speed,
and something about shocks...
妾のスピードがどうとか
ビリビリがどうとか…
What the heck?
なんだそりゃ
Since that girl came to kill
me because I was in the way,
（木更）あの子が 邪魔な私を
消しに来たということは―
there's no doubt there'll be another attack.
２回目の襲撃は 確実にあるわ
The fate of the Tokyo Area is in your hands.
君の手に 東京エリアの命運が
かかっているの
I order you as the president:
社長として命じます
Eliminate the sniper who is
targeting Seitenshi-sama,
聖天子様を狙う狙撃手を排除し
and see justice done.
正義を遂げなさい！
Yeah, I'll stop her.
止めるよ 必ず
I'll be the one to stop her.
あいつは―
俺が止める！
Rentaro, is this going to work?
（延珠）蓮太郎 うまくいくかな？
I'm not sure.
どうだろうな
目くらましぐらいになればいいが
Hopefully it'll be enough to disguise us, at least.
Saitake Sogen...
斉武宗玄
あいつが黒幕に決まってる
He has to be the one behind this.
Satomi-san, that is going too far.
（聖天子）里見さん
それは言いすぎです
He's the one who proposed that meeting,
向こうから会談を持ちかけて
and you were attacked
on the way back from it.
その帰りに襲われたんだぞ
Is playing dumb in spite of that
your way of preserving the peace?
それでも
バカなフリをし続けることが
あんたの言う
平和を体現するってことなのか？
I cannot cancel this meeting
without any proof.
証拠もないのに
会談を中止することはできません
You're going to be killed!
（蓮太郎）ん… 殺されるぞ！
The actions I take are so I do not put shame
私(わたくし)は 国家元首という立場に
恥じぬよう行動しているのです
upon my title as the head of state.
If I am fated to lose my life
because of those actions,
もし それによって
命を落とすのが運命ならば
then I have no choice.
致し方ありません
くっ…
Stop messing around!
（蓮太郎）ふざけんな！
（延珠）蓮太郎！
Rentaro!
I'm going to protect you.
俺は守るぞ
I didn't agree to be your bodyguard
just to let you get killed!
あんたを
みすみす殺させるために
護衛を引き受けたわけじゃない！
あ…
Thank you, Satomi-san...
ありがとう 里見さん
Come on, Princess, let's go.
さあ お姫様 行くぜ
I am not a princess—
私は お姫様ではなく…
（保脇(やすわき)卓人(たくと)）んん…
What is the meaning of this?!
これは どういうことだ
Why is Seitenshi-sama riding
in such a piece of junk?!
なぜ こんな粗末な車に
聖天子様を乗せている！
We switched cars.
車を替えた
I've determined that the
limo is too dangerous.
リムジンじゃ 危険だと判断した
Why, you...
貴様 私に報告もなく
勝手なマネを！
How dare you make that decision
without my permission?!
貴様 私に報告もなく
勝手なマネを！
（虫の羽音のような音）
あ… この音は!?
That sound...
Look out!
危ない！ うっ…
Rentaro!
It's an attack! Protect Seitenshi-sama!
（延珠）蓮太郎！
（保脇）襲撃だ 聖天子様を守れ！
（蓮太郎）うっ…
Rentaro...
蓮太郎…
Enju... watch the back...
延珠 後ろを見張ってくれ
（延珠）あ…
She should still be targeting us.
まだ 狙ってるはずだ
Right, Tina Sprout?
そうだろ ティナ･スプラウト
Tina Sprout...
ティナ･スプラウト…
There's a flash!
光った！
（運転手）うわー！
Go into that parking garage! Hurry!
そこの駐車場に入れ！ 早く！
Rentaro, I will go after that sniper.
蓮太郎 妾があの狙撃手を追う！
Go after her? Can you get there in time?
追うって… 間に合うのか？
If I go alone.
妾だけなら！
Be careful. Come back, no matter what.
気をつけろ 絶対に戻ってこい
Who do you think I am?
妾を誰だと思っているのだ！
I will be back shortly!
すぐ戻る！
Everything's fine... Calm down.
大丈夫だ 落ち着け…
Since the enemy's a sniper,
Enju has a chance.
相手が狙撃手なら 延珠に分がある
And in this darkness...
それに この暗さなら…
（聖天子）ハァ ハァ ハァ…
Why did you come out?!
なんで 出てきたんだ！
Satomi-san, where is Enju-san?
（聖天子）里見さん 延珠さんは？
She went after the sniper alone.
（蓮太郎）狙撃手を追ってる
（聖天子）そんな…
No...
Please call her back immediately!
今すぐ 呼び戻してください
I used my authority
ティナ･スプラウトという名前―
to run an inquiry on the name
Tina Sprout in the IISO.
私の権限で
ＩＩＳＯに照会してみました
She is ranked 97,
彼女は 序列98位
an Owl Initiator, and one
of the mechanized soldiers!
フクロウのイニシエーターで
強化兵士の１人です
If Enju-san is alone, she will be killed!
延珠さんでは 殺されてしまいます
（携帯電話の操作音）
（呼び出し音）
Enju...
（蓮太郎）延珠…
（呼び出し音）
Enju?! Thank goodness...
延珠か!? ああ よかった…
Come back right now! We need to regroup!
今すぐ こっちに戻ってこい！
作戦を立て直す！
Enju? What's wrong? At least answer me!
延珠？ どうしたんだよ
返事くらいしろよ！
Hey, Enju!
おい 延珠！
Is it... Tina?
ティナ… なのか？
Enju
No... Enju...
そんな…
延珠…
♪～
～♪
#07 In the Still of the Moonlit Night, the Dawn Sky
The ones ranked 100 or higher
are unbelievable monsters...
（菫）序列100番以内の連中は
掛値なしの化け物どもだ
Please, don't come here, Rentaro-san...
（ティナ）お願い 来ないで
蓮太郎さん…
Come on, let's end this, Tina!
（蓮太郎）
さあ 決着をつけようぜ ティナ！